[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
But I don't love you.
I don't believe you.
I don't...
Do you really feel nothing?
But your body is telling me
that we feel the same way.
Lie.
You've always been like this.
You just do whatever you want.
I'll tell you one more time.
I don't love you.
Lin Zai.
Don't be like this.
Then tell me.
What exactly should I do
so we can go back to how we were?
Do you know what I need most?
I need a peaceful and stable life,
not to live in fear every day.
I need someone who can understand my fear
and my weakness.
Can you give me that?
You can't even understand it, can you?
But I can learn.
But you've never even thought about
giving up your mission for me, have you?
Where are you going now?
Are you going to see He Yao again?
Even at a time like this, you're still saying things like that.
This just proves that you don't understand me at all.
[Apocalypse Log 18]
Is the water temperature okay?
The water temperature is just right.
He Yao.
You're here, too.
I'm here to try some herbs for Grandma Qiu.
And to give Chen Jin some electrolytes.
Dr. He is so thoughtful.
He's always thinking about my needs.
Thank you so much.
Dr. He is being so helpful to us.
I don't know how to thank you.
Don't mention it, Grandma Qiu.
Lin Zai is my junior.
It's only right that I take care of you.
Junior?
Yes, we're alumni.
It must be fate.
I heard you were in the same camp before.
Yes.
Lin Zai is a real...
Come in.
Lin Zai.
Why are you here at this hour?
Is something wrong?
I want to see my brother.
How is he now?
Still the same.
During the observation period,
his vitals haven't fluctuated abnormally.
Lin Zai, I know you're anxious,
but research requires a focused and undisturbed environment.
In the future, unless I call for you,
try to come here less often.
It's better for your brother's stability
and the continuity of my work.
I just want to see if he's okay.
I didn't mean to disturb your work.
I understand.
Actually, I have something to show you.
Using your blood sample
combined with previous cultures,
I've synthesized a preliminary test fluid.
Theoretically, it can enhance the affinity to specific viral proteins.
Want to see the initial results?
Though, it's only in the testing phase.
Okay.
Follow me.
Help me lift this cloth.
Brother.
Brother, can you hear me?
It's Lin Zai, Brother.
- Brother. - Don't be too anxious.
The test fluid reacted with the virus.
It significantly suppressed the abnormal discharge of motor neurons.
So, his manic state has lessened.
But the infection signal in the core nervous system
has barely decreased at all.
This test fluid is still far from being able to wake him up.
But at least it proves we're on the right track.
However, the dosage, the purity...
Or rather, we haven't found the key that can penetrate the blood-brain barrier
and precisely neutralize the core virus.
It still needs more adjustments.
More tests.
And more of your blood for analysis and optimization.
I understand.
As long as I can save my brother,
no matter how long it takes,
how much time is needed,
or what you need me to do,
I'll cooperate.
He Yao, continue with the experiment.
I'll be fine.
Good. Remember what you said.
And remember, maintaining your own stability
is the key to continuing the experiment.
Where's that boy, Lie?
Why didn't he come for dinner?
Are you two all right?
He looked quite upset today.
He's fine, Grandma.
He... probably just wants to be alone.
Chen, please look after Grandma.
I'll go check on him.
Sure. Go ahead.
Lin Zai.
It's lights out.
Please return to your rooms.
Lock your doors and windows.
Stay safe.
It's lights out.
Please return to your rooms.
Lock your doors and windows.
Stay safe.
It's lights out.
Please return to your rooms.
Lock your doors and windows.
Stay safe.
It's lights out.
Please return to your rooms.
Lock your doors and windows.
Stay safe.
Lin Zai.
It's time to go inside.
The patrol will be doing a headcount soon.
Yeah, I know.
Are you okay?
Lin Zai, are you okay?
I'm fine, Chen.
I'm just a little tired.
I wanted to get some fresh air.
If you're tired, get some rest.
Don't push yourself too hard.
If you're willing to talk, I'm here to listen.
You know...
I said some very harsh things to Lie.
I said he doesn't understand feelings.
And...
And many other hurtful things.
But I had no choice.
I know there's a huge difference between us.
If we continue, nothing good will come of it.
I should be decisive.
Right?
But I still can't let go.
I can't let go.
But what can I do if I can't let go?
I have reasons why I must do this.
Do you feel any discomfort?
Press down on this for five minutes.
I drew a bit more blood than usual.
Drink this.
It's an iron supplement and good for your recovery.
Go back and rest early today.
If you feel dizzy or have palpitations,
lie down immediately.
If you need anything, come find me anytime.
Okay.
Wait.
No rush.
Sit for a while longer.
How is your research going?
Lin Zai, experiments take time.
Your brother will get better day by day.
Then I'll come back tomorrow.
Is that okay?
I want to see him get better soon.
The sooner, the better.
Okay.
But you have to promise me,
take good care of yourself.
Go back and eat more today.
- Get some rest early. - Okay.
Hey.
Do you need me to walk you back?
In your current state,
I'm worried about you being alone.
It's okay. I'll be fine on my own.
[Lin Zai 002]